A Guide to the Virginia Tech and Local History Mounted Clippings, c. 1870s-1960s
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
Virginia Tech and Local History Mounted Clippings, c. 1870s-1960s
Special Collections, Virginia Tech, Blacksburg, Va.
VerticalFile.006
64 Cubic Feet; 147 boxes
In general, the Virginia Tech and Local History Mounted Clippings include newspaper clippings, photocopies, ephermera, unpublished and/or informal publications, and other papers relating to a specific subject area. Files in this collection relate to Virginia Tech, Blacksburg, and the activities of members of the community or university. The collection was primarily collected by library staff through the 1960s.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Acquisition Information
Newman Library staff collected materials for mounted clippings through the 1960s.
Scope and Content
In general, the Virginia Tech and Local History Mounted Clippings include newspaper clippings, photocopies, ephermera, unpublished and/or informal publications, and other papers relating to a specific subject area. Files in this collection relate to Virginia Tech, Blacksburg, and the activities of members of the community or university.
Arrangement
Mounted Clippings are arranged by subject, primarily alphabetically.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Materials
Vertical Files (successors to the mounted clippings):
Biographical Vertical Files
Blacksburg Vertical Files
Montgomery County/Christiansburg Vertical Files
Record Group Vertical Files
Southwest Virginia Vertical Files
Index Terms
Subjects:
Local/Regional History and Appalachian South; University History
Geographic Terms:
Blacksburg (Va.); Montgomery County (Va.)
Organizations:
Virginia Agricultural and Mechanical College; Virginia Agricultural and Mechanical College and Polytechnic Institute; Virginia Polytechnic Institute
Contents List
- Agriculture, 1905-1959
  - General Notes, Ma1-Ma1268, 1905-1959
    Scope and Content
    Ma may include Agricultural Conference Board and Institute Of Rural Affairs.
    - General Notes, Ma1-Ma80 (Box 9)
      Ma 1 may include Agricultural Experiment Station & Field Research Stations. Ma 1, 5, 6, 10, 11, 15, 16 may include Farmers' Institute. Ma 3 may include Corn Day Short Course. Ma 5, 18, 19, 29 may include Farmer'S Winter Short Course. Ma 11, 24 may include Dairy Cattle At V.P.I. Ma 18 may include Planters Club. Ma 19 may include Pure-Bred Sire Campaign. Ma 22 may include Agriculture & Life Sciences, College Of - Poultry Science. Ma 22 may include Boys & Girls Short Course. Ma 23 may include Virginia Aberdeen Angus Breeders' Association. Ma 23, 24, 59, 61 may include Horticulture Club. Ma 25, 28 may include Corn Score Card. Ma 28 may include Dairy Science Club (American Dairy Science Association; Incl. Dairy Clubs). Ma 30, 65 may include Hoof & Horn Club. Ma 61 may include American Society Of Agricultural Engineers. Ma 65 may include Little International Livestock Show.
    - General Notes, Ma81-Ma186 (Box 10)
    - General Notes, Ma187-Ma334 (Box 11)
      Ma 221, 223-233, 239 may include Mccormick, Cyrus Hall Centennial Celebration (1931). Ma 222, 224, 226-228, 259, 262, 264 may include Institute Of Rural Affairs. M 309 may include Alumni Gate.
    - General Notes, Ma335-Ma456 (Box 12)
    - General Notes, Ma457-Ma578 (Box 13)
    - General Notes, Ma579-Ma701 (Box 14)
    - General Notes, Ma702-Ma834 (Box 15)
    - General Notes, Ma835-Ma971 (Box 16)
    - General Notes, Ma972-Ma1111 (Box 17)
    - General Notes, Ma1112-1250a (Box 18)
    - General Notes, Ma1251-Ma1268 (Box 19)
  - Agronomy, MAag1-MAag414
    - Agronomy, MAag1-MAag123 (Box 19)
    - Agronomy, MAag124-MAag234 (Box 20)
    - Agronomy, MAag235-MAag351 (Box 21)
    - Agronomy, MAag352-MAag414 (Box 22)
      MAAg 355 may include Jamestown Centennial Festival (VPI Horticulturists Plant Indian Tobacco).
  - Animal Husbandry, MAAn1-MAAn226
    - Animal Husbandry, MAAn1-MAAn71 (Box 22)
    - Animal Husbandry, MAAn75-MAAn190 (Box 23)
    - Animal Husbandry, MAAn191-MAAn226 (Box 24)
  - Biology-Entomology, MAB.E1-MAB.E117
    - Biology-Entomology, MAB.E1-MAB.E51 (Box 24)
    - Biology-Entomology, MAB.E52-MAB.E117 (Box 25)
  - Biology-Animal Pathology, MAB.API1-MAB.API39
    - Biology-Animal Pathology, MAB.API1-MAB.API39 (Box 24)
  - Biology-Forestry, MAB.F1-MAB.F56
    - Biology-Forestry, MAB.F1-MAB.F53 (Box 25)
    - Biology-Forestry, MAB.F54-MAB.F56 (Box 26)
  - Biochemistry and Nutrition, MABio1-MABio8
    - Biochemistry and Nutrition, MABio1-MABio8 (Box 26)
  - Biology-Plant Pathology, MAB.PP1-MABP20, 1948-1949
    - Biology-Plant Pathology, MAB.PP1-MABP20 (Box 26)
  - Dairy Husbandry, MAD1-MAD219
    - Dairy Husbandry, MAD1-MAD110 (Box 26)
    - Dairy Husbandry, MAD111-MAD219 (Box 27)
  - Agricultural Economics, MAEc1-MAEc263
    MAEc 8, 264 may include Virginia Summer School For Town & Country Ministers.
    - Agricultural Economics, MAEc1-MAEc3 (Box 27)
    - Agricultural Economics, MAEc4-MAEc137 (Box 28)
    - Agricultural Economics, MAEc138-MAEc248 (Box 29)
    - Agricultural Economics, MAEc249-MAEc263 (Box 30)
  - Agricultural Engineering, MAEn 1-MAEn113
    - Agricultural Engineering, MAEn1-MAEn105 (Box 30)
    - Agricultural Engineering, MAEn106-MAEn113 (Box 31)
  - 4-H, MAFH1-MAFH330
    - 4-H, MAFH1-MAFH129 (Box 31)
    - 4-H, MAFH130-MAFH242 (Box 32)
    - 4-H, MAFH243-MAFH330 (Box 33)
  - Home Economics, MAHm1-HAHm177
    - Home Economics, MAHm1-HAHm3 (Box 33)
    - Home Economics, MAHm4-HAHm153 (Box 34)
    - Home Economics, MAHm154-HAHm177 (Box 35)
  - Horticulture, MAHr1-MAHr229a
    - Horticulture, MAHr1-MAHr102 (Box 35)
    - Horticulture, MAHr103-MAHr216 (Box 36)
    - Horticulture, MAHr217-MAHr229a (Box 36)
      MAHr 223 may include Weather.
  - Horticulture-Food Processing, MAHr.F1-MAHr.F12
    - Horticulture-Food Processing, MAHr.F1-MAHr.F12 (Box 37)
  - Horticolture-Garden Short Coarse, MAHr.G1-MAHr.G28
    - Horticolture-Garden Short Coarse, MAHr.G1-MAHr.G28 (Box 37)
  - Institute of Rural Affairs, MAIn1-MAIn115
    - Institute of Rural Affairs, MAIn1-MAIn71 (Box 37)
    - Institute of Rural Affairs, MAIn72-MAIn115 (Box 38)
      MAIn 85, 86 may include Buildings - Hutcheson Hall (Formerly New Agricultural Hall).
  - Miscellaneous, MAM1- MAM276
    MAM 177, 177a, 835, 208, 230a may include Institute Of Rural Affairs. MAM 198, 199, 203-206, 212, 215, 251, 254-260 may include Mccormick, Cyrus Hall. MAM 203, 207, 211, 1957 may include Motion Picture Unit At VPI.
    - Miscellaneous, MAM1- MAM90 (Box 38)
    - Miscellaneous, MAM91- MAM205 (Box 39)
    - Miscellaneous, MAM206- MAM276 (Box 40)
      MAM 264 may include Atoms (Film By VPI "Infant Giant").
  - Poultry, MAP1-MAP96 (Box 41)
    - Poultry, MAP1-MAP45 (Box 40)
    - Poultry, MAP46-MAP96 (Box 41)
  - Plant Pathology an Plant Physiology, MAPP1-MAPP86, 1949-1959
    - Plant Pathology an Plant Physiology, MAPP1-MAPP66 (Box 41)
    - Plant Pathology an Plant Physiology, MAPP67-MAPP86 (Box 42)
  - Articles by VPI Writers, MarG1-MarTil, 1954-1959
    - Articles by VPI Writers, MarG1-MarTil (Box 42)
      Mar O1 may include "Pot Pourri".
  - Agriculture Statistics, MAS1-4, 1949-1959
    - Agriculture Statistics, MAS1-4 (Box 42)
  - Applied Science and Business Administration, Masb1-Masb34, 1950-1959
    - Applied Science and Business Administration, Masb1-Masb42 (Box 42)
      Masb 22 may include High School Science Teachers Summer Institute. Masb 23 may include Conservation Short Course.
  - Vocational Education, MAV1-MAV218
    MAV may include Future Farmers Of America.
    - Vocational Education, MAV1-MAV123 (Box 43)
    - Vocational Education, MAV124-MAV218 (Box 44)
- Blacksburg, 1877-1959
  Mbl may include Community Concert Association and Earthquakes. Mbl 1a, 2, 4, 417, 472, 473, 1438, 1441, 1445, 1564, 1592, 1603 may include "Huckleberry". Mbl 5, 1206-1207 may include Norfolk & Western Railroad. Mbl 1052, 1054, 1189 may include Future Farmers Of America.
  - Blacksburg, Mbl1-Mbl76 (Box 46)
    Mbl 4 may include Sham Battle. Mbl 5 may include American Red Cross. Mbl 9 may include "Solitude".
  - Blacksburg, Mbl77-Mbl209 (Box 47)
    Mbl 77 may include Lakes & Ponds.
  - Blacksburg, Mbl210-Mbl325 (Box 48)
  - Blacksburg, Mbl326-Mbl455 (Box 49)
  - Blacksburg, Mbl456-Mbl590 (Box 50)
  - Blacksburg, Mbl591-Mbl728 (Box 51)
  - Blacksburg, Mbl729-Mbl831 (Box 52)
  - Blacksburg, Mbl832-Mbl926 (Box 53)
  - Blacksburg, Mbl927-Mbl1031 (Box 54)
  - Blacksburg, Mbl1032-Mbl1143 (Box 55)
  - Blacksburg, Mbl1144-Mbl1240 (Box 56)
    Mbl 1206 may include Lybrook Row.
  - Blacksburg, Mbl1240-Mbl1335 (Box 57)
  - Blacksburg, Mbl1336-Mbl1445 (Box 58)
  - Blacksburg, Mbl1446-Mbl1534 (Box 59)
  - Blacksburg, Mbl1535-Mbl1644 (Box 60)
  - Blacksburg, Mbl1645-Mbl1752 (Box 61)
  - Blacksburg, Mbl1753-Mbl1783 (Box 62)
- Board of Visitors, 1914-1959
  - Board of Visitors, Mb0-30 (Box 45)
  - Board of Visitors, Mb31-55 (Box 46)
- Boys' State and Girls' State, 1946-1959
  - Boys'/Girls' State, Mbo1-Mbo90 (Box 62)
  - Boys'/Girls' State, Mbo91-Mbo143 (Box 63)
- Campus Views
  Mcv may include Mall and President's Home.
  - Campus Views, Mcv66-Mcv123 (Box 65)
    Mcv 96 may include Doorways - V.P.I. Buildings. Mcv 99 may include Lakes & Ponds.
  - Campus Views, Mcv124-Mcv130 (Box 66)
    Mcv 130 may include Buildings - R.O.T.C Building (Building 364).
- Commencement and Finals
  - Commencement and Finals, Mfi1-Mfi3 (Box 74)
  - Commencement and Finals, Mfi4-Mfi64 (Box 75)
    Mfi 18 may include Sham Battle. Mfi 23 may include Athletic Department (Formerly Athletic Association); Hoof & Horn Club; and Masons.
  - Commencement and Finals, Mfi65-Mfi176 (Box 76)
    Mfi 74 may include Freshmen. Mfi 120, 149, 151, 157 may include Kohler Trophy.
  - Commencement and Finals, Mfi177-Mfi222 (Box 77)
- Concerts and Plays, 1937-1959
  Mcon may include Community Concert Association.
  - Concerts and Plays, Mcon1-Mcon67 (Box 64)
  - Concerts and Plays, Mcon68-Mcon114 (Box 65)
- Consolidation, 1912-1918
  - Consolidation, Mc1-Mc5 (Box 63)
- Courses of Study, 1877-1959
  - Courses of Study, Mco1-Mco40 (Box 63)
    Scope and Contents
    Mco 4, 7 may include Agriculture & Life Sciences, College Of - Poultry Science.
  - Courses of Study, Mco41-Mco58 (Box 64)
    Mco 57 may include Russian Language Course.
- Dances, 1915; 1918-1959
  - Dances, Mda1-Mda85 (Box 66)
    Mda 2 may include Lynchburg Club. Mda 29 may include Songs Of VPI Incl. Moonlight & VPI, Tech Triumph, Ut Prosim.
- Deaths, 1918-1959
  Mde may include Accidents And Deaths.
  - Deaths, Mde1-Mde9 (Box 66)
    Mde 6 may include Highty-Tighties.
  - Deaths, Mde10-Mde135 (Box 67)
    Mde 28 may include Engineering, Metallurgical.
  - Deaths, Mde136-Mde165 (Box 68)
- Debates (Intercollegiate), 1916-1927; 1948-1959
  - Debates (Intercollegiate), Md1-Md4 (Box 66)
- Development, 1959
  Mdev may include Agriculture & Life Sciences, College Of - Horticulture; Campus Development Plan; and "Pre-Centennial Development Program".
  - Development, Mdev1-Mdev165 (Box 68)
    Mdev 7 may include Arboretum (Sculpture).
- Education Foundation (VPI Education Foundation), 1948-1959
  - Education Foundation, Med1-Med19 (Box 69)
    Med 8-12, 17 may include Mccormick, Cyrus Hall.
- Engineering and Chemistry, 1917; 1930-1949
  Me may include Engineering, College Of, and Geology.
  - Engineering and Chemistry, Me1-Me87 (Box 68)
    Me 9 may include Buildings - Davidson Hall (Chemical Engineering). Me 12 may include Airport (Officially Opened In 1939). Me 72 may include Mall.
  - Engineering and Chemistry, Me88-Me140 (Box 69)
- Enrollment and Registration, 1946-1959
  Menr may include Freshmen and Orientation.
  - Enrollment and Registration, Menr1- Menr25 (Box 69)
  - Enrollment and Registration, Menr26-Menr32 (Box 70)
- Exercises for New Students, 1925-1946; 1951-1959
  - Exercises for New Students, Med1-Med19 (Box 70)
- Extension Schools, 1950-1959
  Mext may include Branch Colleges Of VPI.
  - Extension Schools, Mext1-Mext9 (Box 70)
- Faculty, 1950-1959
  - Faculty, Mf1-Mf49 (Box 70)
    Mf 29 may include Wine Faculty Achievement Award.
  - Faculty, Mf50-Mf180 (Box 71)
  - Faculty, Mf181-Mf315 (Box 72)
  - Faculty, Mf316-Mf424 (Box 73)
    Mf 360, 416 may include Buildings - Seitz Hall (Agricultural Engineering Building).
  - Faculty, Mf425- Mf529 (Box 74)
- Guidance and Placement
  - Guideance and Placement, Mg1-Mg2 (Box 77)
- Korean War, 1950-1953
  - General Notes, W20a1 (Box 111)
  - Casualties and Deaths, W20ca1-W20ca6 (Box 111)
  - Commissions, Honors, etc., W20co1-W20co11 (Box 111)
  - Miscellaneous Individuals, W20m1-W20m12 (Box 112)
  - Blacksburg, W21a1-W21a7 (Box 112)
- Legislation (VPI and the State Legislature), 1900-1959
  - Legislation, Ml1-Ml60 (Box 77)
    ML 1 may include Loans To Students. ML 2, 3, 4, 5 may include Rison Bill. ML 4 may include Engineering Experiment Station. ML 7, 8, 9, 10 may include Bonds, V.P.I. (To Finance Building Of War Memorial Hall).
  - Legislation, Ml61-Ml69 (Box 78)
- Marriages and Engagements
  - Marriages and Engagements, Mme1-Mme70 (Box 88)
  - Marriages and Engagements, Mme71-Mme2071 (Box 89)
- Military, 1875-1959
  Mm may include Uniforms, Military, Armistice Day, Corps Of Cadets, and Military Organizations. Mm 3, 7, 7c, 15, 135 may include Highty-Tighties. Mm 42, 43, 63, 72, 94, 105, 116, 124, 130, 132, 159, 164 may include Kohler Trophy.
  - Military, Mm1-Mm17 (Box 86)
    Mm 14, 16 may include Inspection, Military.
  - Military, Mm18-Mm122 (Box 87)
    Mm 21, 22, 23, 24 may include Foch Celebration. MM 78 may include Air R.O.T.C. Mm 92 may include World War I and World War Ii.
  - Military, Mm123-Mm166 (Box 88)
- Miscellaneous, 1886-1959
  M may include Armistice Day; Art, Dept. Of; Arts & Sciences, College Of [Obsolete]; Class Of (Different Years); Concerts & Plays (Not VPI); Conferences, Seminars, Workshops (Off-Campus); Conferences, Seminars, Workshops (On-Campus); Engineering Exposition; Engineering, College Of; Enrollment & Registration; Highty-Tighties; Horse Show; and Snow Battle. M 10, 119, 802 may include Faculty. M 10, 123, 171 may include Engineering Experiment Station. M 22, 54, 103, 104, 236, 245 may include Fires--On Campus. M 23, 24, 26a, 103, 104 may include Buildings - Field House (1914) (Burned). M 23, 31, 785, 804, 810 may include Buildings - Mcbryde Building Of Mechanic Arts (The Shops). M 23, 245, 805, 862 may include Trees--V.P.I. Campus. M 24, 26, 29, 115, 166, 170a, 195, 214, 218, 222 may include Science Club Obsolete. M 25, 31, 112, 118, 120 may include Maury Literary Society. M 26, 28, 73 may include Farmer's Winter Short Course. M 26, 85, 120, 511 may include Inspection, Military. M 29, 30, 134, 135 may include Grounds (Buildings &). M 31, 40, 95, 99, 113, 115, 132, 215, 236, 240, 241, 242 may include Rat System. M 31, 46, 263 may include Gitt, William G. ("Uncle Bill"). M 54, 113 may include World War I. M 66, 69, 70, 534 may include Songs Of VPI Incl. Moonlight & VPI, Tech Triumph, Ut Prosim. M 71, 738, 759 may include Masons. M 74, 233, 234 may include Student Volunteer Movement. M 77, 134, 139, 275, 369, 371 may include Course Of Study. M 82, 87-89, 134, 157, 226 may include Norfolk & Western Railroad. M 82, 125, 129, 153, 517 may include American Society Of Mechanical Engineers (Asme). M 93, 224, 489 may include American Society Of Agricultural Engineers. M 97, 107a, 113, 120, 121, 123, 131, 773, 774 may include Buildings - War Memorial Gymnasium. M 102, 167, 203 may include Chemical Club / Chemistry Club. M 109, 116, 276 may include Home Demonstration. M 111, 113, 133, 134, 148, 718, 722, 723, 807 may include Buildings - Miles Stadium, 1926-1964. M 115, 116, 135, 138, 148, 139, 785, 804, 810 may include Buildings - Patton Hall. M 115, 168 may include Shenandoah Valley Club. M 122, 182 may include Fertilizer Short Course School M 122, 182. M 125, 178, 240, 193 may include Athletic Department (Formerly Athletic Association). M 127, 138, 176, 194a, 214, 236 may include American Chemical Society (Student Affiliate). M 128, 222, 339, 340, 442 may include Virginia Social Science Association. M 130, 394, 495, 513, 514 may include American Red Cross. M 131, 210, 786, 810, 837 may include Buildings - Academic Buildings 1 & 2. M 134, 148, 149, 160, 182, 184, 185, 195, 238, 273, 276, 278, 318, 331, 438, 447, 464, 465, 470, 471, 481, 498, 849 may include Airport (Officially Opened In 1939). M 135, 293 may include Stroubles Creek (Strubbles Creek). M 135, 330, 356, 398 may include Educators' Conference. M 136, 726, 11/1, 18, 31, 152 may include Dining Halls. M 138, 148, 738, 739, 755, 757, 763, 802 may include Buildings - Henderson Hall (Infirmary). M 140, 141, 147-149, 225, 326, 329, 508 may include Geology. M 140, 149, 835 may include Buildings - Power Plant. M 140, 312, 460 may include Rural Electrification Short Course. M 150, 223, 350, 382, 462, 464 may include Freshmen. M 151, 171, 380, 811 may include Quarries. M 151, 176 may include Lynchburg Club. M 151, 314, 516 may include Lakes & Ponds. M 154-1930 to M 347-1937 may include Rural Minister's Short Course. M 155, 455, 504, 153 may include Virginia Associated Plumbing, Heating, Contractors. M 157, 160, 738, 739, 802, 804, 810 may include Buildings - Saunders Hall (Dairy Science). M 160, 165 may include Engineering, Ceramic. M 161, 163, 173, 179, 189, 203, 337 (Civilian Students Union) may include Student Government Association. M 161, 170, 174 may include Soil Survey (Virginia). M 164, 165, 191, 324 may include Thanksgiving Game. M 173, 267, 309, 390, 433, 436, 610 may include Weather. M 174, 186, 187, 275, 448 may include Engineering, College Of. M 179a, 416 may include Noell Act. M 209, 709, 785, 804, 810, 825, 826, 126, 208 may include Buildings - Davidson Hall (Chemical Engineering). M 220, 223, 397 may include Future Farmers Of America. M 225, 239, 351, 458, 467 may include Home Economics, College Of (Human Resources). M 232, 517, 220, 224 may include Engineering, Metallurgical. M 235, 389 may include Engineering, Chemical. M 271, 886 may include Biology, Dept. Of. M 282a, 312 may include Out-Of-School Youth. M 295, 352 may include Graham Plan (Re: Athletic Aid). M 376, 390, 393, 394, 413, 417, 424, 714, 727, 785, 786, 804, 810, 887, 890, 891 may include Buildings - Owens Dining Hall. M 393, 785, 786 may include Buildings - Eggleston Hall (East Stone Dorm). M 397, 835a may include Institute Of Rural Affairs. M 407, 481 may include Sigma Xi (Honorary Faculty Research Society). M 443, 693 may include Treasury, V.P.I. M 452, 738, 739, 804, 810 may include Buildings - Holden Hall. M 458, 463, 468, 469, 810 may include Buildings - Hillcrest ("Skirt Barn"). M 467, 483, 487, 488, 854, 223 may include Boycotts. M 548, 568 may include Cave Club. M 637, 835, 836, 837, 844 may include Buildings - Dormitories. M 660, 772, 773, 776, 781, 785, 786, 792, 794, 796, 796a, 804, 810, 878 may include Buildings - Williams Hall. M 690, 714, 731, 745, 746 may include Rad-Tech. M 755, 756, 763, 882, 883, 890 may include Buildings - Greenhouse (Dept. Of Horticulture). M 760, 761, 781, 782, 785, 791, 794, 796, 796a, 804, 810, 835, 882, 883, 886, 878, 881 may include Buildings - Randolph Hall. M 760, 772, 774, 835 may include Buildings - Meat & Processing Lab. M 780, 792, 805, 807, 824, 835 may include Buildings - Livestock & Poultry Disease Lab. M 785, 802, 835, 837 may include Buildings - Rasche Hall. M 785, 802, 879 may include Buildings - Brodie Hall and Shanks Hall (No. 4 & No. 7 Barracks United). M 787, 788, 794, 796, 797, 799-801, 804, 806, 810, 811, 819, 820, 823, 824, 827, 830, 832-834, 834a, 835-836 may include Buildings - Library - Carol M. Newman Library. M 810, 815, 868 may include Buildings - Commencement Hall (Old Commerce Hall). M 810, 835 may include Buildings - Seitz Hall (Agricultural Engineering Building). M 880-887, 890, 893, 738, 739, 804, 810 may include Buildings - Robeson Hall.
  - General Notes, M1-M67 (Box 1)
    M 12 may include Christmas Card V.P.I. and Class Ticket. M 17a may include Virginia Agricultural & Mechanical College (Vamc). M 20 may include Pulaski Club. M 22, 37 may include Buildings - Preston & Olin Buildings. M 23, 24 may include Septic Tank. M 30 may include Little International Livestock Show. M 55, 76 may include Hikes - Corps.
  - General Notes, M68-M164 (Box 2)
    M 68, 69, 78, 109, 123, 137, 139 may include Farmers' Institute. M 73 may include Buildings - Alumni Building. M 80, 137 may include Dismissal. M 81, 82, 92, 129 may include American Society Of Civil Engineers. M 88 may include Buildings - Hutcheson Hall (Formerly New Agricultural Hall). M 94 may include Techgram. M 95 may include Mail Service (Campus). M 95, 96, 97, 108 may include Fires--Fought Off Campus. M 108, 155 may include May Day. M 115, 117 may include Buildings - University Club Building (Residence). M 116 may include Agriculture & Life Sciences, College Of - Horticulture. M 116, 117, 120 may include University Club. M 117-118 may include Agriculture & Life Sciences, College Of - Dairy Short Course. M 118 may include State Crop Pest Commission. M 122, 137, 154 may include Electric Meterman's Short Course. M 123 may include Hunt House. M 125 may include Agricultural Students' Honorary Council. M 130 may include United Daughters Of The Confederacy, 1927 Meeting At VPI. M 132 may include Coal. M 138, 139 may include Male Chorus At VPI. M 153 may include Publications, V.P.I.; Sham Battle; and Wine Scholarship. M 153, 154, 155 may include Engineer's Day. M 157 may include Buildings - Print Shop (Old M. E. Laboratory).
  - General Notes, M165-M299 (Box 3)